studentvoice.in 2013-10-03

# Privacy Policy- India Education News Portal

##  [Privacy Policy](http://www.studentvoice.in/p/privacy-policy.html)

Student Voice India is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this web site, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
We may change this policy from time to time by updation of this page. 

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address

What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new  information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

  * We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, ** ** we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

###  Links to other web sites

  * Our web site may contain links to other web sites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

###  Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on Student Voice India, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@studentvoice.in](mailto:info@studentvoice.in)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect

  * The website reserves the right to delete, reject, or otherwise remove any views, opinions and comments posted or part thereof. You shall ensure that the comment is not inflammatory, abusive, derogatory, defamatory &/or obscene, or contain pornographic matter and/or does not constitute hate mail, or violate privacy of any person (s) or breach confidentiality or otherwise is illegal, immoral or contrary to public policy. Nor should it contain anything infringing copyright &/or intellectual property rights of any person(s).

  * The information in these pages does not carry any legal warranty or validity. Any part of data on these pages can be modified unconditionally at any time without prior notification. Use of any information in these pages is under your own risks.

  * Information, Comments, Suggestions, Ideas or Notes submitted by visitors of this website will become a property of the website unless otherwise specified. The web site has all rights to edit, modify or change the information in such a way that it is more useful for general visitors without any change in the meaning or message conveyed by it. ** **
